[
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What is a slowdown lane?",
    "options": [
      "part of the roadway intended for the exclusion of vehicles from the traffic flow on the road",
      "a part of the roadway intended exclusively for the traffic flow of slow vehicles"
    ],
    "answer": "part of the roadway intended for the exclusion of vehicles from the traffic flow on the road"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What is a bike lane?",
    "options": [
      "a part of the pavement intended for bicycle traffic that extends along the pavement and which is marked by a longitudinal line on the pavement and the prescribed traffic sign",
      "a constructed traffic area intended for bicycle traffic that is separated from the road and marked with the prescribed traffic sign"
    ],
    "answer": "a part of the pavement intended for bicycle traffic that extends along the pavement and which is marked by a longitudinal line on the pavement and the prescribed traffic sign"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What is transparency?",
    "options": [
      "the specific space that the road user can see from the place where he is",
      "clear observation of other road users or traffic signs at a certain distance"
    ],
    "answer": "clear observation of other road users or traffic signs at a certain distance"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "At what maximum speed on a road intended exclusively for motor vehicle traffic can a young driver with a category B driving license drive?",
    "options": [
      "at a speed of up to 100 km per hour",
      "at a speed of up to 90 km per hour",
      "at speeds up to 110 km per hour"
    ],
    "answer": "at a speed of up to 90 km per hour"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "How will you act in the situation as in the picture?",
    "options": [
      "go smoothly because the green light has just come on",
      "start carefully and be ready to stop because the truck will stop due to pedestrians",
      "pass the cyclist straight and only then turn right"
    ],
    "answer": "start carefully and be ready to stop because the truck will stop due to pedestrians"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "How you will act in the situation as in the picture",
    "options": [
      "I will overtake the cyclist",
      "I will ride behind the bike until both lines become intermittent"
    ],
    "answer": "I will overtake the cyclist"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "Who is the driver?",
    "options": [
      "a person driving a vehicle on the road",
      "a person qualified as a driver in a driving school"
    ],
    "answer": "a person driving a vehicle on the road"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "When are you required to use dipped headlights instead of high beams?",
    "options": [
      "always while driving on the road outside the settlement",
      "while driving behind another vehicle if the lights of my vehicle dazzle the driver of the vehicle in front of me",
      "before passing another vehicle at the required distance"
    ],
    "answer": "while driving behind another vehicle if the lights of my vehicle dazzle the driver of the vehicle in front of me"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "How do children most often react in traffic?",
    "options": [
      "in accordance with regulations",
      "spontaneous and unpredictable",
      "prudent and calm"
    ],
    "answer": "spontaneous and unpredictable"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": " What does the green flashing light on the traffic light mean?",
    "options": [
      "mandatory stopping",
      "imminent cessation of free passage",
      "the imminent appearance of yellow or red light"
    ],
    "answer": "the imminent appearance of yellow or red light"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": " What must be the minimum width of the free passage on the part of the road from the stopped or parked vehicle and the opposite edge of the pavement?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "4 m"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": " In traffic, according to which participants must the driver not rely on the principle of trust without caution?",
    "options": [
      "towards children",
      "towards participants of the opposite sex",
      "towards persons who are visibly under the influence of alcohol"
    ],
    "answer": "towards children"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": " What are the first signs of driver fatigue?",
    "options": [
      "trembling legs",
      "closing your eyes",
      "yawning"
    ],
    "answer": "yawning"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": " What is the purpose of the device in the picture?",
    "options": [
      "to determine the amount of alcohol in the blood",
      "to determine the amount of alcohol in the exhaled air",
      "to determine the presence of drugs in the body"
    ],
    "answer": "to determine the amount of alcohol in the exhaled air"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " What does this traffic sign mean?",
    "options": [
      "completion of the expressway",
      "completion of the motorway",
      "completion of the state road"
    ],
    "answer": "completion of the expressway"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " What danger does the traffic sign in the picture warn of?",
    "options": [
      "to a dangerous place where wild animals often cross the road at a distance of 600 meters after the traffic sign",
      "to a dangerous place where wild animals often cross the road 600 meters from the traffic sign",
      "to a dangerous place where domestic animals often cross the road 600 meters from the traffic sign"
    ],
    "answer": "to a dangerous place where wild animals often cross the road 600 meters from the traffic sign"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " What should you watch out for when you come across this traffic sign?",
    "options": [
      "on possible vehicles in a bend",
      "to adjust the driving speed",
      "to the narrowing of the road on the left"
    ],
    "answer": "to adjust the driving speed"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " Which traffic sign gives preference to passing vehicles from the opposite direction?",
    "options": [],
    "answer": "a sign with a red arrow pointing up and a black arrow pointing down"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " Which traffic areas in the situation as in the picture are marked in yellow?",
    "options": [
      "bicycle lane",
      "bus stop",
      "bicycle path"
    ],
    "answer": "bus stop"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " What does this additional sign traffic sign indicate?",
    "options": [
      "to the position of the road with the right of way",
      "to a mandatory stop",
      "on the obligatory direction of travel"
    ],
    "answer": "to the position of the road with the right of way"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Crossroads",
    "question": " You are approaching this intersection. How will you proceed?",
    "options": [
      "miss the yellow tram",
      "miss both vehicles",
      "drive first"
    ],
    "answer": "drive first"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Crossroads",
    "question": " How will you act in this situation?",
    "options": [
      "miss a vehicle from the opposite direction",
      "drive first through the intersection"
    ],
    "answer": "drive first through the intersection"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Crossroads",
    "question": " How will you act in this situation?",
    "options": [
      "drive first because I drive straight",
      "miss a motorcycle",
      "miss the bike on the right"
    ],
    "answer": "miss a motorcycle"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Crossroads",
    "question": " How will you act in this situation?",
    "options": [
      "miss cyclists",
      "cyclists have to stop and miss me",
      "estimate the distance of the cyclist in the right side mirror",
      "be sure to turn your head and check the right blind spot"
    ],
    "answer": "miss cyclists"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What is the maximum permitted speed of a vehicle towing another defective vehicle?",
    "options": [
      "40 km per hour",
      "50 km per hour",
      "60 km per hour"
    ],
    "answer": "40 km per hour"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What distracts the driver while driving?",
    "options": [
      "cell phone conversation",
      "air conditioning in the vehicle",
      "reading and writing messages on mobile phones"
    ],
    "answer": "reading and writing messages on mobile phones"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " Drive in the left lane in the situation as in the picture. How will you proceed?",
    "options": [
      "cross the vehicle in the right lane before the pedestrian crossing",
      "accelerate and pass before a pedestrian who encounters a pedestrian crossing",
      "stop and allow a pedestrian to cross the pedestrian crossing"
    ],
    "answer": "stop and allow a pedestrian to cross the pedestrian crossing"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What road features affect driving safety?",
    "options": [
      "greater pavement width",
      "the width of the central longitudinal line",
      "greater width of the traffic lane"
    ],
    "answer": "the width of the central longitudinal line"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " If your vehicle's dashboard lights up and flashing as shown in the picture, what does that mean?",
    "options": [
      "the rear fog light is on",
      "that the engine oil pressure lamp indicates a fault",
      "that all direction indicators on the vehicle are on"
    ],
    "answer": "that all direction indicators on the vehicle are on"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What dangers do you recognize in the situation in the picture?",
    "options": [
      "a sharp turn on the road directed to the right",
      "slippery pavement",
      "possible vehicle drift"
    ],
    "answer": "slippery pavement"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What is the average length of driver response time under normal driving conditions?",
    "options": [
      "one second",
      "three seconds"
    ],
    "answer": "one second"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " How many meters of road must a light beam of fog lights illuminate?",
    "options": [
      "a maximum of 35 meters of road",
      "a maximum of 55 meters of road",
      "maximum 100 meters of road"
    ],
    "answer": "a maximum of 100 meters of road"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What are the consequences of lower tire pressure than prescribed?",
    "options": [
      "reduction of fuel consumption",
      "lengthening of braking distance and poor grip",
      "faster wear and warming of tires"
    ],
    "answer": "faster wear and warming of tires"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What characterizes driving outside the settlement?",
    "options": [
      "riding in columns and numerous overtaking",
      "numerous and different intersections",
      "higher driving speeds"
    ],
    "answer": "higher driving speeds"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What does the light on the instrument panel with the symbol in the picture indicate?",
    "options": [
      "use of seat belt",
      "all direction indicators are on",
      "charging the battery"
    ],
    "answer": "use of seat belt"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What does the 145/80 mark on the tire indicate?",
    "options": [
      "tire width and height",
      "width and outer diameter of the tire",
      "rim diameter and tire height"
    ],
    "answer": "tire width and height"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What is a car accident?",
    "options": [
      "a road event involving at least one moving vehicle",
      "an event on the road in which at least one person was injured or killed",
      "an event on an unclassified road in which a work vehicle landed off the road",
      "an event on the road in which material damage was caused"
    ],
    "answer": "an event on the road in which at least one person was injured or killed"
  },
  {
    "test": "B1",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What does the length of the response path depend on?",
    "options": [
      "on driving speed",
      "on the condition and type of pavement"
    ],
    "answer": "on driving speed"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What is a road?",
    "options": [
      "any public road, street in the settlement and unclassified road on which traffic is performed",
      "any public area on which motor vehicle traffic is performed"
    ],
    "answer": "any public road, street in the settlement and unclassified road on which traffic is performed"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What is traffic endangerment?",
    "options": [
      "such a manner of participation in traffic due to which there was an immediate danger of a traffic accident",
      "an action in traffic by which someone, contrary to traffic regulations, is forced to change the previous way of participating in traffic without the occurrence of an imminent danger of a traffic accident"
    ],
    "answer": "such a manner of participation in traffic due to which there was an immediate danger of a traffic accident"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "Who is a participant in road traffic?",
    "options": [
      "a person who participates in road traffic in any way",
      "a person who in no way participates in road traffic"
    ],
    "answer": "a person who participates in road traffic in any way"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What does the flashing green control indicator light on the instrument panel mean?",
    "options": [
      "that the turn signal is on",
      "that the direction indicators are correct if the lamp flashes at a normal rhythm",
      "dipped beam on"
    ],
    "answer": "that the turn signal is on"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What is a pavement?",
    "options": [
      "longitudinal part of the roadway intended for one-way traffic, with one or more traffic lanes",
      "marked or unmarked part of the roadway whose width is sufficient for unobstructed traffic of one row of vehicles in one direction"
    ],
    "answer": "marked or unmarked part of the roadway whose width is sufficient for unobstructed traffic of one row of vehicles in one direction"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What is the maximum permissible mass of the vehicle?",
    "options": [
      "the mass of the vehicle together with its carrying capacity",
      "mass of the vehicle with cargo in or on the vehicle"
    ],
    "answer": "the mass of the vehicle together with its carrying capacity"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What is a bike path?",
    "options": [
      "a constructed traffic area intended for bicycle traffic that is separated from the road and marked with the prescribed traffic sign",
      "a part of the pavement intended for bicycle traffic that extends along the pavement and which is marked by a longitudinal line on the pavement and the prescribed traffic sign"
    ],
    "answer": "a constructed traffic area intended for bicycle traffic that is separated from the road and marked with the prescribed traffic sign"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "If you are towing a faulty vehicle, may persons be transported in it?",
    "options": [
      "they must not",
      "may"
    ],
    "answer": "they must not"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What is a traffic jam?",
    "options": [
      "action in traffic by which someone is forced to change the previous way of participating in traffic contrary to traffic regulations",
      "such manner of participation in traffic as a result of which there was an immediate danger of a traffic accident"
    ],
    "answer": "such a manner of participation in traffic as a result of which there was an immediate danger of a traffic accident"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": " How do you have to drive at an intersection?",
    "options": [
      "I have to cross the intersection in the lane I was in",
      "they can change the traffic lane at the intersection if necessary"
    ],
    "answer": "I have to cross the intersection in the lane I was in"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": " Does the driver of a passenger car overtake a truck, in the situation as in the picture, properly?",
    "options": [
      "yes, because it is allowed by the markings on the pavement",
      "no, because it is not allowed on the pavement markings"
    ],
    "answer": "yes, because it is allowed by the markings on the pavement"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": " Which categories of vehicles is entitled to be driven by a driver who has been issued a driving license for category B vehicles?",
    "options": [
      "motor vehicles belonging to AM, F and G category",
      "motor vehicles belonging to BE and H category",
      "only motor vehicles belonging to category B."
    ],
    "answer": "motor vehicles belonging to AM, F and G category"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": " How will you determine the speed of driving on roads outside the settlement?",
    "options": [
      "according to the type of road I drive",
      "according to the travel time for which I want to reach the destination",
      "according to the current driving conditions on the road"
    ],
    "answer": "according to the current driving conditions on the road"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": " Drive the car in the right lane in the situation as in the picture. How will you proceed?",
    "options": [
      "keep driving straight",
      "change lanes in the middle or left lane"
    ],
    "answer": "change lanes in the middle or left lane"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " Which of the traffic signs announces the approach to the intersection where traffic is controlled by traffic lights?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " What is marked on the road with a sign as in the picture?",
    "options": [
      "an obstacle on the road",
      "lateral interference on the road",
      "a bend in the road"
    ],
    "answer": "a bend in the road"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " Which motor vehicles may you overtake after this traffic sign?",
    "options": [
      "motorcycles without a trailer",
      "mopeds",
      "tractors"
    ],
    "answer": "mopeds"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " Which traffic sign indicates a traffic ban for all motor vehicles?",
    "options": [
      "A",
      "B",
      "C"
    ],
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " Which vehicles are allowed to use the road marked with this traffic sign?",
    "options": [
      "passenger cars",
      "motorcycles",
      "tractors"
    ],
    "answer": "passenger cars"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Signs",
    "question": " What does this traffic sign indicate to you?",
    "options": [
      "to prohibit one-way traffic",
      "to prohibit traffic in both directions",
      "that traffic flows only from the opposite direction"
    ],
    "answer": "to prohibit one-way traffic"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Crossroads",
    "question": " Why do you have to miss a blue car in a situation like the one in the picture?",
    "options": [
      "because it is located on the right side",
      "because it moves on the road with the advantage of passing",
      "because you are on a side road"
    ],
    "answer": "because it moves on the road with the advantage of passing"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Crossroads",
    "question": " You are approaching an intersection with a vehicle in the situation as in the picture. How will you proceed?",
    "options": [
      "miss only vehicles coming from the right",
      "miss all vehicles moving on that road"
    ],
    "answer": "miss only vehicles coming from the right"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Crossroads",
    "question": " Why do you have to miss a motorcyclist in a situation like the one in the picture?",
    "options": [
      "because it is located on the right side, and it moves on the road with the advantage of passing",
      "because it is located on the right side and is moving on a side road"
    ],
    "answer": "because it is located on the right side, and it moves on the road with the advantage of passing"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Crossroads",
    "question": " How will you act in the situation as in the picture?",
    "options": [
      "miss a motorcycle",
      "ride before the motorcycle"
    ],
    "answer": "ride before the motorcycle"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What must be the tire pressure?",
    "options": [
      "according to the prescribed instructions of the vehicle manufacturer",
      "according to the prescribed vehicle speed markings",
      "according to the prescribed markings for the carrying capacity of the vehicle"
    ],
    "answer": "according to the prescribed instructions of the vehicle manufacturer"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " Drive in the left lane in the situation as shown. What is the traffic area to the left of the lane you are driving?",
    "options": [
      "bicycle path",
      "bicycle lane",
      "hiking trail"
    ],
    "answer": "bicycle path"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " A police officer raised his hand on the road as in the picture. How will you proceed?",
    "options": [
      "stop immediately",
      "continue driving"
    ],
    "answer": "stop immediately"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " When the red control indicator illuminates for driving on the instrument panel, as in the picture, what will you do?",
    "options": [
      "disconnect the vehicle from traffic",
      "check the oil level in the engine",
      "switch off the engine"
    ],
    "answer": "switch off the engine"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " What are the driving requirements in the city?",
    "options": [
      "constant attention and anticipation of danger",
      "timely observation and response",
      "driving without respect and tolerance"
    ],
    "answer": "constant attention and anticipation of danger"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " At the intersection, you intend to turn left. How will you get by with a vehicle that also turns left from the opposite direction?",
    "options": [
      "miss the vehicle on my right",
      "miss the vehicle on my left"
    ],
    "answer": "miss the vehicle on my right"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " On the road you are driving, work is being carried out in the situation as in the picture. How will you proceed?",
    "options": [
      "continue driving in the traffic lane for vehicles from the opposite direction",
      "stop because the traffic lane I am driving on is busy"
    ],
    "answer": "stop because the traffic lane I am driving on is busy"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " According to the position of the vehicle in the middle lane, what can the driver of the vehicle do in the situation as in the picture?",
    "options": [
      "turn right",
      "go straight through the crossroads",
      "turn left"
    ],
    "answer": "go straight through the crossroads"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " Are you allowed to overtake a vehicle approaching a marked pedestrian crossing?",
    "options": [
      "I must not, because it is not allowed",
      "I may, if there are no pedestrians at the marked pedestrian crossing"
    ],
    "answer": "I must not, because it is not allowed"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " Where are the prescribed values of air pressure in vehicle tires most often recorded?",
    "options": [
      "in the space for markings on vehicle tires",
      "on the fuel filler flap",
      "in the traffic license"
    ],
    "answer": "on the fuel filler flap"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " Drive in the middle lane in the situation as shown. How will you proceed?",
    "options": [
      "drive straight without changing lanes",
      "stop and pass pedestrians intending to cross the roadway",
      "change lanes in the right lane and continue driving straight ahead"
    ],
    "answer": "drive straight without changing lanes"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " Drive in the right lane where the markings are as shown. How will you proceed?",
    "options": [
      "change the lane in the left lane without obstructing the vehicle",
      "regardless of vehicles behind and next to change lane"
    ],
    "answer": "change the lane in the left lane without obstructing the vehicle"
  },
  {
    "test": "B2",
    "category": "Special Features and Hazards",
    "question": " You intend to turn left at the crossroads. What do you have to do?",
    "options": [
      "drive before vehicles coming from the opposite direction",
      "miss vehicles coming straight from the opposite direction or turning right"
    ],
    "answer": "miss vehicles coming straight from the opposite direction or turning right"
  },
  {
    "test": "B3",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What characterizes a road intended exclusively for motor vehicle traffic?",
    "options": [
      "safe traffic flow of vehicles at least 60 km per hour",
      "movement of motor vehicles only",
      "acceleration and deceleration lane"
    ],
    "answer": "movement of motor vehicles only"
  },
  {
    "test": "B3",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "Why is a rough pavement curtain more favorable than a smooth one?",
    "options": [
      "because the tires fit better on it",
      "because the braking distance is shorter",
      "because the shorter the response time of the driver"
    ],
    "answer": "because the braking distance is shorter"
  },
  {
    "test": "B3",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What does the light bulb on the instrument panel with the symbol in the picture indicate?",
    "options": [
      "front fog light on",
      "dipped beam on",
      "rear fog light on"
    ],
    "answer": "rear fog light on"
  },
  {
    "test": "B3",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "What road features outside the settlement affect the increase in driving safety?",
    "options": [
      "sharp bends and downhills",
      "greater width of the road",
      "good transparency"
    ],
    "answer": "greater width of the road"
  },
  {
    "test": "B3",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "Drive on the road in the situation as in the picture. What cross marked across?",
    "options": [
      "bus stop",
      "pedestrian island",
      "marked pedestrian crossing"
    ],
    "answer": "marked pedestrian crossing"
  },
  {
    "test": "B3",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "hat is a traffic lane?",
    "options": [
      "a marked or unmarked part of the roadway the width of which is sufficient for the unimpeded movement of one row of motor vehicles in one direction",
      "longitudinal part of the roadway intended for one-way traffic, with one or more traffic lanes"
    ],
    "answer": "a marked or unmarked part of the roadway the width of which is sufficient for the unimpeded movement of one row of motor vehicles in one direction"
  },
  {
    "test": "B3",
    "category": "Fundamental Issues",
    "question": "How many pavement lanes does the road have in the situation as in the picture?",
    "options": [
      "one",
      "two",
      "three"
    ],
    "answer": "one"
  }
]